{
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "name": "Game of Thrones",
      "quote": "'When you play the game of thrones, you win or you die. There is no middle ground.'",
      "quoteSource": "Season 1, Episode 7",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "What are the house words of House Stark?",
          "choices": ["The North Remembers",
            "When the snows fall and the white winds blow, the lone wolf dies but the pack survives",
            "Winter is Coming",
            "The winters are hard, but the Starks will endure"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Ned Stark's Valyrian greatsword?",
          "choices": ["Longclaw",
            "Oathkeeper",
            "Heartsbane",
            "Ice"],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "Which of these names is not on Arya's list?",
          "choices": ["Cersei",
            "Roose Bolton",
            "Joffery",
            "Illyn Payne"],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the house words of House Targaryen?",
          "choices": ["Fire cannot kill a dragon",
            "Blood of the Dragon",
            "All men must die, but we are not men",
            "Fire and Blood"],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "What or who kills Khal Drogo in the end?",
          "choices": ["The witch, Mirri",
            "His bloodriders",
            "Daenerys suffocates him",
            "His chest wound"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "When Jon first meets Tyrion, what advice does Tyrion give him?",
          "choices": ["“It’s not easy being drunk all the time. If it were easy, everyone would do it.”",
            "“Never forget what you are, the rest of the world will not. Wear it like armor and it can never be used to hurt you.”",
            "“It’s hard to put a leash on a dog once you’ve put a crown on its head.”",
            "“A mind needs books like a sword needs a whetstone.”"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the house words of House Lannister?",
          "choices": ["Hear me roar!",
            "A Lannister always pays his debts",
            "Teach them what it means to put a lion in a cage",
            "When you play a game of thrones, you win or you die"],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "Buffy the Vampire Slayer",
      "quote": "'In every generation there is a chosen one... she alone will stand against the vampires, the demons and the forces of darkness. She is the slayer.'",
      "quoteSource": "Season 1, Episode 1",
      "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Who is the first vampire that Buffy kills in the first episode, 'Welcome to the Hellmouth'?",
          "choices": ["Darla",
            "Luke",
            "Jesse",
            "Thomas"],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "What gift does Angel give Buffy for her 17th birthday?",
          "choices": ["A silver cross",
            "A book",
            "A Claddagh ring",
            "Takes her ice skating"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "In the episode 'Where the Wild Things Are', the gang goes to find Giles for help. They find him singing and playing guitar at the Espresso Bar. What song is he performing?",
          "choices": ["Behind Blue Eyes",
            "Freebird",
            "Tales of Brave Ulysses",
            "Wild Horses"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "Xander tells Anya to dress up as something scary in the Halloween episode 'Fear, Itself'. What does she dress up as?",
          "choices": ["A nurse",
            "A clown",
            "A demon",
            "A bunny"],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "What name do Willow and Tara give their kitten?",
          "choices": ["Trixie",
            "They haven't found her name",
            "Miss Kitty Fantastico",
            "Joan"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What phrase is not on Buffy's tombstone?",
          "choices": ["She saved the world a lot",
            "Beloved Daughter",
            "Devoted Friend",
            "Beloved Sister"],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "In the episode 'Restless', what does Tara warn Buffy?",
          "choices": ["'Be back before dawn.'",
            "'You don't understand.'",
            "'You're asking the wrong questions.'",
            "'Don't stick out your elbow.'"],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "What does Dawn get Tara for her birthday in the episode 'Family'?",
          "choices": ["A spellbook",
            "A witch Pez dispenser",
            "A necklace",
            "A crystal ball"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        }
      ]
    },
      {
        "name": "Parks and Rec",
        "quote": "'We need to remember what's important in life: friends, waffles, work. Or waffles, friends, work. Doesn't matter, but work is third.'",
        "quoteSource": "Season 3, Episode 13",
        "questions": [
          {
            "question": "What is the title of the book Leslie writes?",
            "choices": ["Failure: an American Success Story",
              "Pawnee: The Greatest Town in America",
              "Off the Sidelines: Raise Your Voice, Change the World",
              "A History of Pawnee, Indiana"],
            "correctAnswer": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What word and description appears at the very top of the Swanson Pyramid of Greatness?",
            "choices": ["Capitalism - God's way of determining who is smart, and who is poor",
              "Discipline - The ability to repeat a boring thing over and over",
              "Buffets - Whenever available. Choose quantity over quality",
              "Honor - If you need it defined, you don't have it"],
            "correctAnswer": 3
          },
          {
            "question": "Which of these is not one of Andy's own secrets he tells Ron after finding out about Duke Silver?",
            "choices": ["'I'm allergic to sushi. Every time I eat more than 80 pieces, I throw up'",
              "'I don't know who Al Gore is and at this point I'm too afraid to ask'",
              "'When they say 2% milk, I don't know what the other 98% is'",
              "'I didn't actually sell my last car, I just forgot where I parked it'"],
            "correctAnswer": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What superhero costume does Ben buy when Donna and Tom bring him along on their annual 'Treat Yo Self' day?",
            "choices": ["Superman",
              "Spider-man",
              "Batman",
              "Captain America"],
            "correctAnswer": 2
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the only thing Ron hates more than lying?",
            "choices": ["Clear alcohols",
              "Salad",
              "Cats",
              "Skim milk"],
            "correctAnswer": 3
          },
          {
            "question": "What is April's favorite band?",
            "choices": ["Neutral Milk Hotel",
              "Scarecrow Boat",
              "The Duke Silver Trio",
              "Mouse Rat"],
            "correctAnswer": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "name": "Twin Peaks",
        "quote": "'I have no idea where this will lead us. But I have a definite feeling it will be a place both wonderful and strange.'",
        "quoteSource": "Season 2, Episode 18",
        "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Who discovers Laura Palmer's body?",
          "choices": ["Sheriff Harry S. Truman",
            "Doc Hayward",
            "Hank Jennings",
            "Pete Martell"],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of Agent Cooper's secretary, who he addresses on most of his recordings?",
          "choices": ["Lucy",
            "Margaret",
            "Diane",
            "Nadine"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the diner Shelly works at?",
          "choices": ["Great Northern Diner",
            "Double R Diner",
            "Roadhouse",
            "Bookhouse Diner"],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "What is Agent Cooper's favorite type of donut?",
          "choices": ["Bearclaw",
            "Boston Creme",
            "Jelly",
            "Cruller"],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the Log Lady's real name?",
          "choices": ["Margaret Lanterman",
            "Catherine Martell",
            "Annie Blackburn",
            "Nadine Hurley"],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        }
      ]
    }
  ]     
}
